<stories>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>NYT &gt; Washington</source>
        <imageUrl>http://graphics.nytimes.com/images/section/NytSectionHeader.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.nytimes.com/2008/03/30/washington/30bailout.html?ex=1364616000&amp;en=a879bab8f325b6c3&amp;ei=5090&amp;partner=rssuserland&amp;emc=rss</url>
        <title>Homeowners Pleas Put G.O.P. Lawmakers in Bind on Defaults</title>
        <pulltime>1206880673915</pulltime>
        <length>121</length>
        <description>Some Republicans are stuck between constituents demanding protection from foreclosure and party leaders urging restraint.</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Republican Party</tag>
        <tag score="1">Mortgages</tag>
        <tag score="1">House of Representatives</tag>
        <tag score="1">Diaz-Balart, Lincoln</tag>
        <tag score="1">Foreclosures</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>NYT &gt; Washington</source>
        <imageUrl>http://graphics.nytimes.com/images/section/NytSectionHeader.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.nytimes.com/2008/03/30/magazine/30wwln-Q4-t.html?ex=1364616000&amp;en=a9052f80c7969912&amp;ei=5090&amp;partner=rssuserland&amp;emc=rss</url>
        <title>Questions for Paul O'Neill: Market Leader</title>
        <pulltime>1206880673918</pulltime>
        <length>180</length>
        <description>The former Treasury secretary talks about how the Bush administration mismanaged the crisis in financial markets, his relationship to Dick Cheney and what happened to Bear Stearns.</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Treasury Department</tag>
        <tag score="1">Morgan, J P, Chase &amp; Co</tag>
        <tag score="1">Wall Street (NYC)</tag>
        <tag score="1">Cheney, Dick</tag>
        <tag score="1">Credit</tag>
        <tag score="1">Federal Reserve System</tag>
        <tag score="1">Cayne, James E</tag>
        <tag score="1">O'Neill, Paul H</tag>
        <tag score="1">Bush, George W</tag>
        <tag score="1">Finances</tag>
        <tag score="1">Washington (DC)</tag>
        <tag score="1">Bear Stearns Cos|BSC|NYSE</tag>
        <tag score="1">Blackstone Group|BX|NYSE</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>NYT &gt; Washington</source>
        <imageUrl>http://graphics.nytimes.com/images/section/NytSectionHeader.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.nytimes.com/2008/03/30/science/space/30low.html?ex=1364616000&amp;en=4f37806dadb4c962&amp;ei=5090&amp;partner=rssuserland&amp;emc=rss</url>
        <title>G. David Low, 52, Astronaut and Aerospace Executive, Dies</title>
        <pulltime>1206880673918</pulltime>
        <length>94</length>
        <description>Mr. Low flew three space shuttle missions and later became an executive in the space industry.</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Space</tag>
        <tag score="1">Low, G David</tag>
        <tag score="1">Space Shuttle</tag>
        <tag score="1">National Aeronautics and Space Administration</tag>
        <tag score="1">Deaths (Obituaries)</tag>
        <tag score="1">Cornell University</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>NYT &gt; Washington</source>
        <imageUrl>http://graphics.nytimes.com/images/section/NytSectionHeader.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.nytimes.com/2008/03/30/us/politics/30campaign.html?ex=1364616000&amp;en=6fabddfa231d45f7&amp;ei=5090&amp;partner=rssuserland&amp;emc=rss</url>
        <title>Political Memo: Iraqi Offensive Revives Debate for Campaigns</title>
        <pulltime>1206880673918</pulltime>
        <length>137</length>
        <description>The wars return to the public consciousness poses new challenges and opportunities for the candidates, particularly Senator John McCain.</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Iraq</tag>
        <tag score="1">Presidential Election of 2008</tag>
        <tag score="1">McCain, John</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>NYT &gt; Washington</source>
        <imageUrl>http://graphics.nytimes.com/images/section/NytSectionHeader.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.nytimes.com/2008/03/30/us/politics/30obama.html?ex=1364616000&amp;en=cc678b8d2482e3d1&amp;ei=5090&amp;partner=rssuserland&amp;emc=rss</url>
        <title>Clinton Shouldnt Feel Forced to Quit Race, Obama Says</title>
        <pulltime>1206880673918</pulltime>
        <length>133</length>
        <description>Senator Barack Obama had a few words of advice Saturday for his rival, Senator Hillary Rodham Clinton: Do not drop out on my account.</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Clinton, Hillary Rodham</tag>
        <tag score="1">Presidential Election of 2008</tag>
        <tag score="1">Obama, Barack</tag>
        <tag score="1">Pennsylvania</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>YatPundit</source>
        <url>http://www.yatpundit.com/archives/2007/11/dear-tightassed.html</url>
        <title>Dear tight-assed Northern woman:</title>
        <pulltime>1206880674542</pulltime>
        <length>214</length>
        <description>Unlike wherever you came from originally, New Orleanians are, by and large, a friendly lot. We tell people good morning when we pass by on the sidewalk. People are more likely to wave at someone in a car when at...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">New Orleans Stuff</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>YatPundit</source>
        <url>http://www.yatpundit.com/archives/2007/11/trent-lott-quit.html</url>
        <title>Trent Lott, Quitter</title>
        <pulltime>1206880674542</pulltime>
        <length>238</length>
        <description>No big surprise. Even though he's from Pascagoula, Northrup Grumman's new hero is Mary Mary, since she's in the majority. Trent's brother-in-law is one of the biggest trial lawyers on the gulf coast, and he's suing State Farm on behalf...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">National Politics</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>YatPundit</source>
        <url>http://www.yatpundit.com/archives/2007/11/what-does-marke.html</url>
        <title>What does Markey-Marc have on these guys?</title>
        <pulltime>1206880674542</pulltime>
        <length>207</length>
        <description>OK, so rather than give up Marc, Pampy gave up Oliver, and now Oliver gets 37 months because he won't cooperate. Morial's boy threw Thomas under the bus, yet he's going to be a stand-up guy to the tune of...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Local Politics</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>YatPundit</source>
        <url>http://www.yatpundit.com/archives/2007/12/buying-new-orle.html</url>
        <title>Buying New Orleans Stuff This Christmas</title>
        <pulltime>1206880674542</pulltime>
        <length>237</length>
        <description>a Kossack was wondering if I could suggest some places where people could buy New Orleans stuff, thereby helping boost the New Orleans economy. I've come up with a few ideas: Cafe du Monde - http://shop.cafedumonde.html - full line of...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">New Orleans Stuff</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>YatPundit</source>
        <url>http://www.yatpundit.com/archives/2007/12/hopefully-hell.html</url>
        <title>Hopefully he'll die in prison...</title>
        <pulltime>1206880674542</pulltime>
        <length>226</length>
        <description>...because this is so wrong. The death penalty rarely works in our system of justice, but some people really should be put down like mad dogs: A 33-year-old North Carolina man has been sentenced to 110 years in prison after...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Legal Issues</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>YatPundit</source>
        <url>http://www.yatpundit.com/archives/2007/12/not-even-listed.html</url>
        <title>not even listed???</title>
        <pulltime>1206880674542</pulltime>
        <length>222</length>
        <description>I wonder if DWI enforcement is still off the NOPD radar. It's certainly not for the JPSO, but this study would have looked at Orleans Parish stats: We looked at annual death rates due to alcoholic liver disease, as well...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">New Orleans Stuff</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>YatPundit</source>
        <url>http://www.yatpundit.com/archives/2007/12/taking-ownershi.html</url>
        <title>Taking Ownership of New Orleans</title>
        <pulltime>1206880674542</pulltime>
        <length>251</length>
        <description>Of the various efforts being undertaken to rebuild New Orleans, few are as vocal as activists opposing the demolition of public housing projects. Their passion is strong, and their cause just. I wrote about my problems with this movement yesterday....</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">National Politics</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/259681103/following-action-in-basra-and-iraq.html</url>
        <title>Following the action in Basra and Iraq</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675556</pulltime>
        <length>264</length>
        <description>Gorilla's Guides and Long War Journal are useful sites for news and comments from Iraq.</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Iraq</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/260196256/wto-and-antigua-follow-up.html</url>
        <title>WTO and Antigua follow up</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675556</pulltime>
        <length>1944</length>
        <description>Arstechnica had thoughts on WTO mediation and US indignation about IP rights.The second case concerns Antigua and Barbuda, a small Caribbean country home to all sorts of online vices, including gambling and DRM circumvention. Antigua took the US to the WTO years ago over charges that the US was unfairly criminalizing access to Antiguan gambling websites while still allowing US-based horse racing sites to function. The WTO ruled against the US on several occasions, including a 2007 ruling that found the US had not yet bothered to comply with previous rulings.In retaliation, Antigua has announced a radical plan in an ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Antigua</tag>
        <tag score="1">WTO</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/260214458/call-my-people.html</url>
        <title>Call my people...</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675556</pulltime>
        <length>1111</length>
        <description>Dani Rodrik writes:How bad things get at HarvardAn e-mail from the assistant to an incredibly distinguished Harvard colleague (names deleted to protect the innocent):X [very distinguished Harvard professor] asked me to see if he can get on your calendar to have a lunch with him and Y [another distinguished professor] in the near future. I say that of course, knowing that X's calendar is incredibly complicated, but I am happy to try to offer times if you give me some of your calendar constraints.Now wait a minute. Let me see if I get this straight. X would like to have ...</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/260264578/john-mccain-phil-gramm-and-us-financial.html</url>
        <title>John McCain, Phil Gramm, and the US Financial Crisis</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675556</pulltime>
        <length>2768</length>
        <description>Paul Krugman picks up on the implications of McCain relying on Phil Gramm as an economic advisor. Id rather see Gramm the fiscal hawk advising McCain on spending and tax policy than the free lunch hack named Art Laffer even if Gramm would balance the budget with spending cuts than tax increases. But its reform of the financial system that is at issue in Pauls post. As Politico notes:The general co-chairman of John McCains presidential campaign, former Sen. Phil Gramm (R-Texas), led the charge in 1999 to repeal a Depression-era banking regulation law that Democrat Barack Obama claimed on Thursday ...</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/260310207/basra-force-ratios.html</url>
        <title>Basra force ratios</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675556</pulltime>
        <length>262</length>
        <description>fester at Newshoggers has a post on military aspects of the conflict in Basra and Baghdad.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/260459010/smart-way-out-of-foolish-war.html</url>
        <title>The Smart Way Out of a Foolish War</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675556</pulltime>
        <length>7081</length>
        <description>I know it is not fashionable to praise former members of the Carter Administration but I have always admired how Zbigniew Brzezinski expresses his views. While I dont always agree with him his latest on the Iraq mess is exactly right on several issues. First - why did we invade Iraq?The case for U.S. disengagement from combat is compelling in its own right. But it must be matched by a comprehensive political and diplomatic effort to mitigate the destabilizing regional consequences of a war that the outgoing Bush administration started deliberately, justified demagogically and waged badly.President Bush did start this ...</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/260656385/banning-comments.html</url>
        <title>Banning Comments</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675556</pulltime>
        <length>5511</length>
        <description>Angrybear has had a tradition of allowing a free flow of comments. Other blogs have not and I find the following quite interesting. From Boing Boing's Moderation Policy:Q. What's likely to land me in your bad graces?A. Since you've asked, here's a nowhere-near-exhaustive list:1. Spamming. Linkwhoring. Re-posting text you've already posted on a dozen other sites.2. Making supercilious and unpleasant remarks in a civil liberties thread about how the victim had it coming. This is not to say that victims never have it coming; but there's a species of internet demi-troll that appears to specialize in posting such comments. Try ...</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/259583747/solving-problems-is-attitude-hard-to.html</url>
        <title>Solving problems is an attitude hard to find</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675557</pulltime>
        <length>2295</length>
        <description>The NYT carries a story about forclosures in a Baltimore neighborhood, and an outreach program to help people save their homes. I have quoted the part that interests me.Statistics on foreclosure are snapshots of a moving phenomenon, and data from the state labor department show 174 foreclosures in Belair-Edison last year, while the Community Law Center, a nonprofit public service group, counted 181; both figures are well below the more than 275 foreclosures in 2001 and in 2002. Because of a difference in counting the 2006 figures, the state number represents an increase in 2007, but a decline over several ...</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Angry Bear</source>
        <url>http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/blogspot/Hzoh/~3/259583748/occ-and-model-validation-part-2.html</url>
        <title>OCC and Model Validation Part 2</title>
        <pulltime>1206880675557</pulltime>
        <length>3490</length>
        <description>FIRE reports:The securities industry is an economic powerhouse that continues to strengthen the U.S. economy, said Securities Industry Association President Marc Lackritz. SIA data shows that last year alone, we raised a record $3.2 trillion of capital for American business and nearly $14 trillion over the past five, underscoring our substantial contribution to overall growth in the U.S. economy.Also fatbear in comments earlier offers this link by Paul Krugman on the OCC and Office for Thrift Supervision.Just go read Krugman from right before Xmas last year:Consider the press conference held on June 3, 2003 just about the time subprime lending ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">OCC</tag>
        <tag score="1">regulation</tag>
        <tag score="1">model validation</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2006/11/fast-food-news-podcast-pictures-on.html</url>
        <title>Fast Food News Podcast: Pictures on Video Version</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>995</length>
        <description>Click To Play A special presentation of the Fast Food News audio podcast...with pictures! Hosts Jay and James take you on a romp through fast food headlines, news, trends, trivia and features such as the Sandwich of the Week.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2006/11/podcast-fast-food-news-1.html</url>
        <title>Podcast: Fast Food News #1</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>1241</length>
        <description>Show #1Listen/downloadFeature on the Quizno's Steak Sandwich.The Burger of the Week is the A W Teenburger: the bacon has been know to cut Jay's face.Dehydrated, reconstituted onions on McDonald's hamburgers and cheeseburgers are actually a delicious way to eat an onion.In Fast Food News Headlines this week: A W is now serving deep fried corn dog 'bits.'Canadian fast food chain Harvey's pulls out of the Regina and it's Home Depot location.What would you take with your from the fast food world if you knew you were going to be stranded on a desert island?Jay would take the kentucky Fried Chicken ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">podcasts</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2006/11/podcast-fast-food-news-3.html</url>
        <title>Podcast: Fast Food News #3</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>1829</length>
        <description>The special today: Fast food breakfasts!The Sandwich of the Week is the Enormous Omlette Sandwich at Burger King, weighing in at 730 calories. It's huge! And deadly!The only fast food item from a major chain to intimidate our experienced hosts. It's not like we can't finish it. As Jay says, looking at an Enormous Omelette Sandwich is like looking down a toboganning hill. You know you're going to finish, you just don't know what kind of shape you'll be at the end.The essential breakfast sandwiches, according to Jay--you'll be surprised.The McGriddle overdoses Jay: it gives him an unhealthy feeling.And a ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">podcasts</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2006/11/whistle-dog-from-w.html</url>
        <title>The Whistle Dog from A &amp; W</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>3731</length>
        <description>The Whistle Dog from A W was featured as the Sandwich of the Week on the FFN #4 last week. However, we forgot to include the nutritional information at that time because it was unavailable to us. But we do have it now so here it is: Whistle Dog 195 480 3 34 27 28 12 .5 TOTAL 195 480 3 34 27 28 12 .5 It has nearly the same fat and calories as a Big Mac (North American version of the Big Mac) but isn't nearly as filling for most robust eaters. The Whistle Dog may be a ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">nutrition</tag>
        <tag score="1">info</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2007/02/fast-food-news-no-7-rats-in-nyc.html</url>
        <title>Fast Food News No. 7: Rats in NYC!</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>633</length>
        <description>Special Breaking News Edition Regina's Fast Food News TV has sent a reporter to the scene in NYC where rats have taken over a KFC-Taco Bell. Includes the original raw footage of the rats as well as exclusive new audio from the scene. Not suitable for young children. Link to MOV QuickTime for iTunes/iPod players or download.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2007/02/it-wrap-innovation-at-mcdonald.html</url>
        <title>It's a wrap: innovation at McDonald's</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>133</length>
        <description>Continue reading...</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2007/02/join-our-fast-food-news-youtube-group.html</url>
        <title>Join our Fast Food News YouTube Group</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>99</length>
        <description>YouTubers, come join our group here.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Fast Food News Podcast</source>
        <url>http://www.reginaradio.com/fastfood/2007/03/video-response-to-dairy-queen-ad.html</url>
        <title>Video response to Dairy Queen ad</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688300</pulltime>
        <length>1126</length>
        <description>Click To Play James's video response to the DQ Flame Thrower Burger, the highest calorie, highest fat burger from any major chain. link to QuickTime video</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Associated Press business headlines via GoUpstate.com</source>
        <url>http://www.goupstate.com/article/20080330/APE/803300510&amp;source=rss</url>
        <title>TV, Film Actors' Unions Sever Ties</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688651</pulltime>
        <length>231</length>
        <description>Unions representing film and television actors will negotiate separately with producers in upcoming contract talks after board members of the TV actors union voted Saturday to sever a long-standing agreement between the two guilds.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Associated Press business headlines via GoUpstate.com</source>
        <url>http://www.goupstate.com/article/20080330/APW/803300532&amp;source=rss</url>
        <title>Administration Pushes Regulatory Changes</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688651</pulltime>
        <length>199</length>
        <description>The Bush administration is trying to confront the credit crisis that has rattled nerves from Wall Street to Main Street by proposing wholesale changes in how Washington oversees the financial system.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Associated Press business headlines via GoUpstate.com</source>
        <url>http://www.goupstate.com/article/20080329/APA/803290525&amp;source=rss</url>
        <title>Airlines Lighten Up to Cut Fuel Costs</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688652</pulltime>
        <length>292</length>
        <description>Your ginger-ale doesnt come in a glass anymore on most US Airways flights. On Delta youll find yourself in a thinner, lighter seat. If you fly JetBlue cross-country, youll get a dainty bag of 100-calorie crisps in place of the original snack box of cookies, crackers and spreadable cheese.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Associated Press business headlines via GoUpstate.com</source>
        <url>http://www.goupstate.com/article/20080329/APF/803290566&amp;source=rss</url>
        <title>Washington, Wall St. Tangle on Oversight</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688652</pulltime>
        <length>162</length>
        <description>One of the casualties of the ongoing credit crisis is a long-held notion on Wall Street - that the investment banking community can take care of its own problems.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Associated Press business headlines via GoUpstate.com</source>
        <url>http://www.goupstate.com/article/20080329/APF/803290568&amp;source=rss</url>
        <title>Weak Economy Slows Cargo, Idles Railcars</title>
        <pulltime>1206880688652</pulltime>
        <length>179</length>
        <description>BNSF Railway Co., the nations top hauler of container rail freight, is parking miles of railcars in Montana and elsewhere because there isnt enough freight to keep them rolling.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source></source>
        <url>http://frontier.userland.com/1999/08/21</url>
        <pulltime>1206880689598</pulltime>
        <length>479</length>
        <description>The UserLand Frontier Kernel is a powerful development platform including an integrated object database, scripting language, a script editor and debugger, outliner, a multi-threaded runtime and an integrated HTTP server. UserLand's Kernel is the low-level technology behind the commercial products Manila and Radio UserLand -- time and market tested, world-class web content management systems.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=1214e26d-674e-4a5c-b716-eaa07d327705</url>
        <title>Looking for a word here ....</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>2987</length>
        <description>We have a bit of a wording problem. With what I am current building we have a bit (not precisely) a notion of "tail calls". Here's an example: public void LookupMessage(int messageId) { MessageStoreService messageStore = new MessageStoreService(); messageStore.LookupMessage(messageId); } The call to LookupMessage() doesn't return anything as a return value or through output parameters. Instead, the resulting reply message surfaces moments later at a totally different place within the same application. At the same time, the object with the method you see here, surrenders all control to the (anonymous) receiver of the reply. It's a tiny bit like ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Architecture|SOA</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=12693f85-3f44-48e9-8921-0d7ddaca88cf</url>
        <title>Prankster. Ah. Right.</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>2299</length>
        <description>News is what is made news. Point in case: This sentence on my blog here: "There's apparently a related project Boa (another serpent name along the family line of Viper that was the original codename for MTS), including the business markup language BML (pronounced "Bimmel") that he's involved in and he talked a bit about that, but of course I'd be killed if I gave out more details." now prompts, directly or indirectly, this here on Microsoft Watch and this on eWeek. Nobody said that the project was software in product development. Nobody said it was about stuff that ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Blog</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=514bac78-5c4e-4c57-9c15-e7736c83aa1d</url>
        <title>Naming and Continuations (continued)</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>10268</length>
        <description>I was a little off when I compared my problem here to a tail call. Gordon Weakliem corrected me with the term "continuation". The fact that the post got 28 comments shows that this seems to be an interesting problem and, naming aside, it is indeed a tricky thing to implement in a framework when the programming language you use (C# in my case) doesn't support the construct. What's specifically tricky about the concrete case that I have is that I don't know where I am yielding control to at the time when I make the respective call. I'll ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Architecture</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=6215302e-b279-4e35-96ab-fc4d9bd4eedc</url>
        <title>A word from us, my sponsor: newtelligence SOA Workshop in Dsseldorf, October 13-15 2004</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>4071</length>
        <description>newtelligence AG will be hosting an open workshop on service-oriented development, covering principles, architecture ideas and implementation guidance on October 13-15 in D #252;sseldorf, Germany. The workshop will be held in English, will be hosted by my partner and #8220;Mr. Methodologies #8221; Achim Oellers and myself, and is limited to just 15 (!) attendees to assure an interactive environment that maximizes everyone #8217;s benefit. The cap on the number of attendees also allows us to adjust the content to individual needs to some extent. We will cover the #8220;services philosophy #8221; and theoretical foundations of service-compatible transaction techniques, scalability ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Architecture</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=a13d9b2b-f96d-4b24-a876-e52597e4b73a</url>
        <title>BOA/BML</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>1009</length>
        <description>AAMOF, BOA along with BML are PBS TLA's created when we were TUI and MSU while having a late dinner. TMA in this industry and way too much fuzzy MBS. TWOP! IAR, giving out SSI under NDA would get me into VDS, get me?. (You can speculate all you want in the comments section). (c)2002-2004 Clemens Vasters. You want to build service oriented applications on the Microsoft .NET Framework and are not quite sure how? newtelligence Workshops get you going with concrete, pragmatic guidance on today's shipping technology stack, keeping tomorrow in perspective. Available on-site, world-wide. Tell me more!</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Other Stuff</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=b6d6b110-62a1-49af-a0bd-4a94ed8ff3be</url>
        <title>New on board at newtelligence</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>865</length>
        <description>Daniel Fisher aka "Lenny Bacon" joined the pack and is already having some fun. (c)2002-2004 Clemens Vasters. You want to build service oriented applications on the Microsoft .NET Framework and are not quite sure how? newtelligence Workshops get you going with concrete, pragmatic guidance on today's shipping technology stack, keeping tomorrow in perspective. Available on-site, world-wide. Tell me more!</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">newtelligence</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=c3f73593-4636-4906-bee7-a1f0e90159f7</url>
        <title>Microsoft enforcing its patent portfolio on Open Source? How likely is it that?</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>7960</length>
        <description>Microsoft Watch highlights the recently surfaced HP memo that speculates that Microsoft would start enforcing its patent portfolio on Open Source. How likely is it? It is an interesting question, indeed. Here #8217;s what I think: The patent situation, especially on the middleware market, used to be very much like the cold war between the USSR and the USA in the last century. One side moves, everyone dies. My guess is that if Microsoft had gone out and dragged Sun to court over J2EE and Sun had countersued over .NET, things would have gotten really, really nasty. The very ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">IT Strategy</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=c9e5630a-bf19-4187-b85b-cc825c6450c9</url>
        <title>An early, early morning for the .NET Rocks Show</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>1261</length>
        <description>Carl invited me for .NET Rocks on Thursday night. That is July 15th, 10 PM-Midnight Eastern Standard Time (U.S.) which is FOUR A.M. UNTIL SIX A.M. Central European Time (CET) on Friday morning. I am not sure whether my brain can properly operate at that time. The most fun thing would be to go out drinking Thursday night ;-) I want to talk about (guess what) Services. Not Indigo, not WSE, not Enterprise Services, not SOAP, not XML. Services. Mindset first, tools later. (c)2002-2004 Clemens Vasters. You want to build service oriented applications on the Microsoft .NET Framework and ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Architecture</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=cf1bc0c7-05e4-4aec-a47a-7127ac849bf9</url>
        <title>http://radio.weblogs.com/0108971 soon out of business</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>2669</length>
        <description>Adieu, Userland. Ladies, if you haven #8217;t switched your feeds to this address yet (it #8217;s a year now), now #8217;s the time. UPDATE: I've mirrored a few old stories from over there. The rest of the content is here anyways. -----Original Message----- From: customerservice@userland.com [mailto:customerservice@userland.com] Sent: Friday, July 09, 2004 12:10 AM To: Clemens F. Vasters Subject: Radio UserLand Renewal Reminder Greetings from the community server for Radio UserLand 8. This is a reminder that your Radio UserLand serial number will expire soon. This is the third renewal-reminder email. You will receive two subsequent reminders, one the day ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Blog</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=e37002f1-7d22-4270-aa9f-487417237b66</url>
        <title>Architect's Introspection</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>732</length>
        <description>Do I do this because I want to or do I do this because I need to? (c)2002-2004 Clemens Vasters. You want to build service oriented applications on the Microsoft .NET Framework and are not quite sure how? newtelligence Workshops get you going with concrete, pragmatic guidance on today's shipping technology stack, keeping tomorrow in perspective. Available on-site, world-wide. Tell me more!</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Architecture</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=f24c4e77-c717-4dca-9d75-495688048ff5</url>
        <title>Addressing insight over beer</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>2782</length>
        <description>I might be blind to not have seen that before, but this here hit me over the third Guinness at an Irish Pub while answering a sudden technical question from my buddy Bart: wsa:ReplyTo xmlns:wsa="http://schemas.xmlsoap.org/ws/2004/03/addressing" wsa:Address http://server/service_second_intermediary /wsa:Address wsa:ReferenceProperties wsa:ReplyTo wsa:Address http://server/service_first_intermediary /wsa:Address wsa:ReferenceProperties wsa:ReplyTo wsa:Address http://server/service_outer_caller /wsa:Address /wsa:ReplyTo /wsa:ReferenceProperties /wsa:ReplyTo /wsa:ReferenceProperties /wsa:ReplyTo Read the EPR binding rules section 2.3 in the WS-Addressing spec and you'll find out just like me how distributed "call-stacks" work with WS-Addressing, if your choice of communication pattern is the far more flexible duplex (or here) pattern for datagram-based message conversations instead of the ...</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Technology|Web Services</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>Clemens Vasters: Enterprise Development &amp; Alien Abductions</source>
        <url>http://staff.newtelligence.net/clemensv/PermaLink.aspx?guid=f6a0ff09-2c85-4bc7-b278-659d96f78eee</url>
        <title>Got caught</title>
        <pulltime>1206880690619</pulltime>
        <length>778</length>
        <description>Jimmy Nilsson is really good at spotting flamebait. (c)2002-2004 Clemens Vasters. You want to build service oriented applications on the Microsoft .NET Framework and are not quite sure how? newtelligence Workshops get you going with concrete, pragmatic guidance on today's shipping technology stack, keeping tomorrow in perspective. Available on-site, world-wide. Tell me more!</description>
    <tags>
        <tag score="1">Architecture</tag>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>IBM DeveloperWorks: XML</source>
        <imageUrl>http://www.newsisfree.com/HPE/Images/button.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.newsisfree.com/iclick/i,271446337,874,f/</url>
        <title>Tip: Perform trackbacks with PHP</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691421</pulltime>
        <length>368</length>
        <description>: Combine the PEAR Services_Trackback package and PHP for an easy way to manually create trackbacks to help blog readers find your related content.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>IBM DeveloperWorks: XML</source>
        <imageUrl>http://www.newsisfree.com/HPE/Images/button.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.newsisfree.com/iclick/i,268974968,874,f/</url>
        <title>DITA topic specialization: Analyze your content and build a specialized DTD</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691422</pulltime>
        <length>324</length>
        <description>: Learn how to create a specialization of a DITA topic type that best fits your needs in this tutorial.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>IBM DeveloperWorks: XML</source>
        <imageUrl>http://www.newsisfree.com/HPE/Images/button.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.newsisfree.com/iclick/i,268974971,874,f/</url>
        <title>XML processing in Ajax, Part 2: Two Ajax and XSLT approaches</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691422</pulltime>
        <length>371</length>
        <description>: Experiment with two more approaches to the Ajax weather badge. Both use XSLT transformations -- one on the server side and the other in the browser.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>IBM DeveloperWorks: XML</source>
        <imageUrl>http://www.newsisfree.com/HPE/Images/button.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.newsisfree.com/iclick/i,269925231,874,f/</url>
        <title>XML processing in Ajax, Part 3: JSON and avoiding proxies</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691422</pulltime>
        <length>384</length>
        <description>: In the last installment, use a public Web service, JavaScript ObjectNotation (JSON), and dynamic script tags for the final approach to the weather badge project.</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>IBM DeveloperWorks: XML</source>
        <imageUrl>http://www.newsisfree.com/HPE/Images/button.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://www.newsisfree.com/iclick/i,271446335,874,f/</url>
        <title>developerWorks forums - XQuery and XPath forum</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691422</pulltime>
        <length>384</length>
        <description>: Find help with XQuery, XPath 2.0, and related recommendations, plus tips and tricks to get the most from these technologies with DB2 and other implementations. .</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | UK</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/nb/74288_16x9_nb.ram</url>
        <title>Lily leads Brit nominations</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691672</pulltime>
        <length>118</length>
        <description>Teenage singer Lily Allen leads the field for the Brit Awards 2007, shortlisted for four prizes. Duration: 01:27 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | UK</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/nb/74291_16x9_nb.ram</url>
        <title>New bill on organised crime</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691672</pulltime>
        <length>120</length>
        <description>New powers to restrict those suspected of organised crime are being introduced by the Home Office. Duration: 01:13 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | Entertainment</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/nb/74141_16x9_nb.ram</url>
        <title>Big haul for Brits at Globes</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691909</pulltime>
        <length>111</length>
        <description>Dame Helen Mirren has won two Golden Globes as part of a big haul for British performers. Duration: 02:07 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | Entertainment</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/nb/74219_16x9_nb.ram</url>
        <title>Skype founders launch net TV</title>
        <pulltime>1206880691909</pulltime>
        <length>100</length>
        <description>The people behind Skype have launched a broadcast quality internet TV service. Duration: 02:13 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | Headlines</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/nb/74255_16x9_nb.asx</url>
        <title>Third terror suspect 'on run'</title>
        <pulltime>1206880692186</pulltime>
        <length>111</length>
        <description>Another terror suspect on a control order has absconded, the Home Secretary has admitted. Duration: 01:55 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | Headlines</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/nb/74275_16x9_nb.asx</url>
        <title>Womb transplant grows nearer</title>
        <pulltime>1206880692186</pulltime>
        <length>112</length>
        <description>Doctors in New York say they are moving closer to being able to perform a womb transplant. Duration: 01:26 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | Headlines</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/nb/74291_16x9_nb.asx</url>
        <title>New bill on organised crime</title>
        <pulltime>1206880692186</pulltime>
        <length>120</length>
        <description>New powers to restrict those suspected of organised crime are being introduced by the Home Office. Duration: 01:13 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
    <story score ="1.0">
        <source>BBC News | Audio Video | UK</source>
        <imageUrl>http://news.bbc.co.uk/nol/shared/img/bbc_news_120x60.gif</imageUrl>
        <url>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/bbcnews.benmetcalfe.com/av/rss/-/media/avdb/news/video/74000/bb/74288_16x9_bb.ram</url>
        <title>Lily leads Brit nominations</title>
        <pulltime>1206880692440</pulltime>
        <length>118</length>
        <description>Teenage singer Lily Allen leads the field for the Brit Awards 2007, shortlisted for four prizes. Duration: 01:27 mins</description>
    <tags>
    </tags>
    </story>
</stories>
